concrete.org 2005-12-12

# American Concrete Institute Privacy Policy

Information Collected 

There are two types of information collected from customers and members of ACI—information _involuntarily_ supplied when a user accesses an ACI web site and information voluntarily supplied when a user completes a form, requests information, or places an order. 

Information collected from you is used to provide the service requested. Some of this information may be retained for future use to enable ACI to provide future services or inform you of new services or information of interest to those in the concrete community. 

Access to Your Information  

Except as described in this policy, when you supply personal information to ACI, you share that information only with ACI and the authorized agents it has retained to implement transactions. 

How We Work to Keep Information Secure  

ACI takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, we make commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information both online and off-line. Because of the nature of the Internet, ACI cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to ACI. You provide all such information at your own risk. 

E-mail  

ACI does not release e-mail addresses to outside organizations. ACI members and customers may opt out of all promotional e-mail communication. All ACI created and supported promotional e-mails have "unsubscribe" instructions. 

Postal Mail  

From time to time, ACI may release names and mailing addresses to outside organizations for promotional or informational purposes. All customers who do not want their name released to outside organizations have the opportunity to select a “no mail” option. 

The names and mailing addresses of members and customers may be rented to outside organizations for the purposes of sending mailing packages that have been screened by authorized ACI staff for their suitability. Materials must be of an educational nature for ACI to rent its list. ACI licenses mailing list usage for one-time only use, and renters are asked to sign their agreement to this practice. 

Cookies   

ACI websites may use cookies to store and help track your information. Cookies are pieces of information that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Information from Server Logs  

As the ACI web site is used, our server records information about the session. This information includes such things as the web site from which your inquiry originated, what browser you are using, the country from which you accessed the Internet, the time and date of your visit, how long your session lasted, what pages you visited, and your Internet Service address. This allows us to serve you better. 

The information from our server logs is used to learn about web site visitors as a group, not about you as an individual. We use IP addresses and other user information to analyze trends, administer the site, track usage of areas of the site, and gather broad demographic information. 

Cooperation with Law Enforcement and Legal Process  

ACI cooperates with governmental agencies and other third parties to enforce laws. ACI will disclose information as we believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that may be illegal or may expose ACI, its authorized agents, or you to possible legal liability. We also provide records and information as may be required by a subpoena. 

Opt-out for European Union and Other Users   

Transfer to the United States: The servers for ACI’s websites are located in the United States. By entering information on this site, you are consenting to the transfer of that information to the United States. Your information will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

In accordance with EU and other guidelines, you may decline to provide the information requested by ACI. Please be advised, however, that ACI may be unable to provide certain benefits and/or services unless such information is provided for security and identification purposes. 

Children  

ACI does not intentionally or knowingly collect information from children. ACI neither identifies information as originating from children nor does ACI market its goods and services to children. 

Modifications  

This policy may change over time as the institute modifies or expands its services. Therefore, users are advised to review this policy from time-to-time to maintain an up-to-date understanding of how information supplied is handled. 

Correct/Update Personal Information  

ACI allows you to change or modify your personal information by visiting ACI's address change form. 

Questions  

Your privacy is important to us. If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of the ACI web site, please contact the ACI [Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@concrete.org) at American Concrete Institute, 38800 Country Club Dr, Farmington Hills, MI, 48331; Phone: (248) 848-3700.
